Good morning.
Want to remind you that Views for Amanda Land goes live at 10 a.m. Eastern on YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
Today we'll be talking about a number of things, including one of the most idiotic statements I've ever heard.
And it was made by Kamala Harris in referring to Donald Trump as a communist fascist on national television.
That's who y'all wanted to be president.
Wow.
We will also be discussing the attack of the global summit flotilla and we'll also have the pleasure of being joined by a being joined by a being joined by a being joined by Adwoa Asante and her client.
And Ronak, who is finally out of jail, but who was actually imprisoned for who is in prison for doing pro-Palestine for doing pro-Palestine graffiti.
So we've got all that going on, as well as Katie LaFoon, who will join us to talk about discovering a massive ICE detention facility in the middle of a California desert and what that could really mean.
So we've got all that talking about all that going on at 10 a.m. Eastern.
Remember, the show is on YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
So even though you'll be able to hear my voice here on Instagram, you won't be able to experience the show in the way that it really needs to be in full with the music and the chat and also the guests.
So I'll see you there at 10 a.m. Eastern at YouTube, Amanda Seals TV for views from Amanda Land.